http://www.bcit.ca/privacy/

Skip to main content
Privacy
BCIT’s website and personal information
When you visit BCIT’s website, BCIT’s web servers automatically collect information that is essential to operating and maintaining the site’s security. The information collected includes:
Browser type
IP address
Some portions of the BCIT website may distribute small pieces of information (called “cookies”) to web browsers to assist you when you return to specific areas on the site. If you have concerns about cookies, you can change your web browser settings not to accept this information, or display warning messages.
BCIT’s website contains links to third party sites, and BCIT is not responsible for the privacy provisions of those other websites.
When you voluntarily send electronic mail to BCIT or complete an electronic form that includes identifying information about you, BCIT will keep a record of this information so that we can respond to you.
BCIT and the protection of personal information
As a public body, BCIT complies with privacy provisions of BC’s Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (RSBC 1996 ch. 165):
Personal information is collected directly from the individual about whom it relates
Personal information is collected, used, and disclosed for purposes consistent with BCIT’s program and service offerings
Individuals have the right of access to and a right to request correction of their own personal information
Personal information is retained for the time period to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected
Personal information is secured from unauthorized access
Individuals will be notified about the purposes for which information is collected, and when information is collected for an optional use, individuals will consent to the information collection
You may refer to BCIT’s policy 6700 Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy [PDF], for more information.
For more information about BCIT’s privacy procedures you may contact:
